<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide Maramures</string>

    <!-- Tourist Attractions page title -->
    <string name="tourist_attraction">Main Attractions</string>

    <!-- Wooden churches page title -->
    <string name="wooden_churches">Wooden Churches</string>

    <!-- Museums page title -->
    <string name="museums">Museums</string>

    <!-- Accommodation page title -->
    <string name="accommodation">Accommodation</string>

    <!-- Tourist attractions -->
    
    <!-- Baia Mare -->
    <string name="baia_mare_title">Baia Mare</string>
    <string name="baia_mare_description">Baia Mare is the capital of Maramures county and Romania’s fourth largest city.
        It is located at the base of the Gutai Mountains and is famous for being a gold-mining town in the 14th century,
        becoming a metals centre under the communists. There is the city park, a theatre,and The Village
        Museum which showcases the renowned traditional wooden houses or the Maramures region.</string>

    <!-- Merry Cemetery -->
    <string name="merry_cemetery_title">Merry Cemetery</string>
    <string name="merry_cemetery_description">
        Located in Sapanta, The Merry Cemetery is famous for its colourful painted tombstones describing
        the people buried there, along with scenes from their lives. The unusual feature of this cemetery
        is that it diverges from the prevalent view, culturally shared within European societies,
        of death as something indelibly solemn.
        </string>
    
    <!-- Mocanita narrow gauge steam train  -->
    <string name="mocanita_steam_train_title">Mocanita Steam Train</string>
    <string name="mocanita_description">Mocanita (Romanian-“Mocăniţa“) is the Romanian forestry narrow
        gauge steam train that was born more than 100 years ago. This line is still the only forestry
        line working in Romania on daily bases in the Water Valley (Valea Vaserului), Viseu de Sus.
        Several steam locomotives are still operating on this line and one of these (764-211, “Mariuta“)
        is over 100 years old! The locomotives are used for both passenger and log trains.</string>

    <!-- Wooden churches -->

    <!-- Surdesti wooden church -->
    <string name="surdesti_title">The wooden church of Surdesti</string>
    <string name="surdesti_description">The wooden church of Şurdeşti, devoted to the
        Saint Archangels Michael and Gabriel, was built in 1721 under the direction of Toma Macarie.
        The church steeple is among the tallest old wooden structures in the world.
        In the past, people believed that the taller the church tower was,
        the easier their prayers could reach up to Heaven.</string>

    <!-- Ieud wooden church -->
    <string name="ieud_title">The wooden church of Ieud</string>
    <string name="ieud_description">The upper church of Ieud, inscribed in UNESCO\'s World Heritage List,
        is made of fir tree wood. Historians have failed to agree on the date of its construction.
        The most cautious suggest the 17th century. Others date it as far back as 1364 and deem it
        to be the oldest in Maramures.</string>

    <!-- Plopis wooden church -->
    <string name="plopis_title">The wooden church of Plopis</string>
    <string name="plopis_description">The wooden church of Plopiş is also part of UNESCO World Heritage
        and is devoted to the Saint Archangels Michael and Gabriel, whose celebration every year is held
        on November the 8th. The village of Plopiş, situated in the Cavnic Valley, is first mentioned
        in documents in 1583, as a settlement belonging to the Chioar Fortress.</string>


    <!-- Museums -->

    <!-- Sighet Village Museum -->
    <string name="sighet_village_title">Sighet Village Museum</string>
    <string name="sighet_village_description">Located as you enter the town of Sighet, on the road from Baia Mare,
        the Village Museum, as you see it today, leaves the impression of a typical village from Maramures.
        One straight road and several crooked roads or paths make up the inherent structure of the settlement
        and they all converge as in all Maramures villages, towards the church.
        The wooden homes of hand-hewn timbers represent Jewish, Slavic, Hungarian, German, and Romanian
        habitations from the 17th and 18th centuries. The houses are preserved intact both inside and out,
        with original carving on the doorways, and some of the writing in Cyrillic and even Arabic.
        \n<b>Opening hours:</b>
        \n\t Tuesday to Sunday from 8AM to 4PM
        \n\t Mondays closed
        \n<b>Contact:</b>
        \n\t Muzeului Street, no. 1, Sighetu-Marmatiei
        \n\t Maramures, Romania
        \n\t Telephone: +40 (0) 262314229
        \n\t E-mail: muzeulmaramuresului@yahoo.com </string>

    <!-- Sighet Memorial of the Victims of Communism and of the Resistance-->
    <string name="sighet_memorial_title">The Memorial of the Victims of Communism and of the Resistance</string>
    <string name="sighet_memorial_description">Located in Sighetu-Maramatiei, the former prison is today
        the setting for a museum dedicated to what happened under communism in Romania and the other
        countries of Central and Eastern Europe.
        The cells have been transformed into museum rooms, each with its own theme or chronology of the
        political malformation that brought suffering and death throughout the twentieth century,
        both inside and outside prison walls.
        \n<b>Opening hours:</b>
        \n\t Monday to Sunday from 9:30AM to 6:30PM
        \n<b>Contact:</b>
        \n\t Corneliu Coposu Street, no. 4, Sighetu-Marmatiei
        \n\t Maramures, Romania
        \n\t Telephone: +40 (0) 262319424
        \n\t E:mail: muzeu@memorialsighet.ro </string>

    <!-- Baia Mare Ethnography and Folk Art Museum -->
    <string name="ethnography_museum_title">Ethnography and Folk Art Museum</string>
    <string name="ethnography_museum_description">Located in Baia Mare, at the foot of the Florilor Hill,
        the Ethnography and Folk Art Museum reflects the traditional occupations, crafts,
        folk clothing and religious objects specific to old Maramures.
        \n<b>Opening hours:</b>
        \n\t Tuesday to Sunday from 10AM to 6PM
        \n\t Mondays closed
        \n<b>Contact:</b>
        \n\t Dealul Florilor Street, no. 1, Baia Mare
        \n\t Maramures, Romania
        \n\t Telephone: +40 (0) 262276895 </string>

    <!-- Accommodation -->

    <!-- The Village Hotel -->
    <string name="village_hotel_title">The Village Hotel in Breb, Maramures</string>
    <string name="village_hotel_description">The Village Hotel is set in over one hectare of land in the heart
        of the village of  Breb,  in Northern Transylvania. There is a stream that runs though the center,
        surrounded by fruit trees and the organic gardens.
        \n<b>Contact:</b>
        \n\t The Village Hotel, no. 349, Breb
        \n\t Maramures, Transylvania, Romania, 437206
        \n\t Bookings: info@villagehotel.ro
        \n\t www.villagehotelmaramures.com
    </string>

    <!-- Babou Hostel -->
    <string name="babou_hostel_title">Babou Hostel</string>
    <string name="babou_hostel_description">Babou’s campsite is situated in the garden behind our
        house where we have around 6000 square metres available for tents and campers.
        We have 14 electricity points, each of 4 ampere. You can choose where you want to pitch your
        tent or place your camper. You can also make use of our hammocks  to sit back and relax or make
        a fire at one of the fire places.
        \n<b>Contact:</b>
        \n\t Babou Hostel, no. 149, Breb
        \n\t Maramures, Transylvania, Romania, 437206
        \n\t Telephone: +40(0)768397339
        \n\t Bookings: info@baboumaramures.com
        \n\t www.baboumaramures.com

    </string>
</resources>